<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on WrayFi</title>
    <link>wrayfi.github.io/www/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on WrayFi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 00:00:05 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="wrayfi.github.io/www/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Problem Description</title>
      <link>wrayfi.github.io/www/project/problem-description/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 00:00:05 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>wrayfi.github.io/www/project/problem-description/</guid>
      <description>Problem we want to solve We are answering the question why fi sucks? By creating a heat map of your wifi, you can test different router placements and find one that optimizes your connectivity.
Importance: Faster internet connection promises impressive gains in productivity (HuffPost) Optimal router placement is a problem intriguing to gaming enthusiasts, business people and the average cal student.
Challenge  Modeling radio waves instead of light rays Every material in the scene is now a lil transparent We have to model different levels of opaqueness Radio waves have phases that can cause interference  Solution Use Radiosity techniques to render wifi signals interacting with different surfaces</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goals and Deliverables</title>
      <link>wrayfi.github.io/www/project/goals-and-deliverables/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 00:00:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>wrayfi.github.io/www/project/goals-and-deliverables/</guid>
      <description>Plan to deliver:  Create a basic 2d heatmap showing wifi distribution from a birds eye view. Essentially a non-interactive version of the project here. How to measure the quality / performance of the system  Measure scene based on real world router locations and test wifi signals against simulated data.  What questions do you plan to answer with your analysis?  How do signals interact/interfere when there are multiple routers?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>wrayfi.github.io/www/project/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 00:00:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>wrayfi.github.io/www/project/schedule/</guid>
      <description>In this section you should organize and plan the tasks and subtasks that your team will execute. Since presentations are ~4 weeks from the due-date of the proposal, you should include a set of tasks for every week.
Week1 Make key design decisions * Research/compare radiosity, widening camera field of view in terms of extensiveness of changes required for proj 3-2 as well as the quality of the heat map produced with each.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>wrayfi.github.io/www/project/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 00:00:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>wrayfi.github.io/www/project/resources/</guid>
      <description>Reference projects
 Router as camera Wifi trace WIFI-Trace  Resources
 Radiosity resource Project 3-2  Hardware:
 VR headset (in case we do Extremely ambitious)  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>