<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Milestones on WrayFi</title>
    <link>https://wrayfi.github.io/www/milestone/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Milestones on WrayFi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 22:39:17 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://wrayfi.github.io/www/milestone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Challenges</title>
      <link>https://wrayfi.github.io/www/milestone/challenges/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 22:39:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wrayfi.github.io/www/milestone/challenges/</guid>
      <description>Challenges:  Initially, we aimed to model the router as the camera. However, the case of multiple routers was not well suited to this model. Instead we decided to have one camera above the scene looking down in a birds eye view. We place the devices around the scene and have the wifi router be the light source. We also pivoted from having a heat map of wifi signals as the final product to a prescription of where you should place your wifi routers based on the hot spots:) in your room, in terms of wifi usage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goals and Deliverables</title>
      <link>https://wrayfi.github.io/www/milestone/goals-and-deliverables/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 00:00:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wrayfi.github.io/www/milestone/goals-and-deliverables/</guid>
      <description>What we have accomplished:  We added an element of energy drop-off to the project3-2 raytracer to model radio waves instead of light rays. The drop-off both as a function of time and of the materials the ray has passed through Created a test scene with some new material modeling.  The three materials we chose to model are  glass(a material that lets rays through some of the time) , mirror (which in the case of wifi, is most similar to aluminum, reflecting rays most of the time), and concrete(a material that largely absorbs wifi rays)).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>https://wrayfi.github.io/www/milestone/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 00:00:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wrayfi.github.io/www/milestone/schedule/</guid>
      <description>Updated work plan: This week:  Go to office hours to really understand the light model and what needs to be tweaked  Implement modifications to ray that model it more as a radio wave than a light wave  Create a scene with the “cellphones” on the highly used regions of the room. Show their brightness changes relative to where the wifi router is placed
Endgame: Get light sources to move around the edge of the room</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slides</title>
      <link>https://wrayfi.github.io/www/milestone/slides/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 23:18:05 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wrayfi.github.io/www/milestone/slides/</guid>
      <description>Slides</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video</title>
      <link>https://wrayfi.github.io/www/milestone/video/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 23:18:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wrayfi.github.io/www/milestone/video/</guid>
      <description>Video</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>